Uh, hey Mike. First of all,
congratulations and welcome to Las
Vegas. Uh, my question for you is just
what do you what do you like about the
opportunity of pairing up as Genty in
the backfield? I know Clint Kubak
mentioned before that he kind of want to
have a wingman for Genty. So, what do
you how how happy are you to kind of
join this backfield with him?
>> I mean, I'm super excited, you know, to
get, you know, get rolling with him. All
I could think of is Thunder and
Lightning. So, super super excited to,
you know, be the uh, you know, one-two
punch with him and, you know, to really,
you know, like I said before, be a
sponge and learn from him also at the
same time.
>> Mike, this is Hondo Carpenter.
Congratulations on making it to the NFL,
but you are not only compact and tough,
but super fast. And there is a lot of
reports about your 40 speed, all of them
exceptional. What is the best that
you've ran the 40 in?
Um, so that was my my PR time was um at
the combine. So about a week and a half
before that I ran a 434 and um I had PR
at the combine with a 4-33.
>> Hey Mike, Jesse Merrick with Silver and
Black Sports Network. I'm just curious
what it is about your skill set that you
think fits into the scheme that Kubak's
going to be running here with a lot of
that wide zone looks and stuff like
that.
Um, well, coming from a a a pro style
offense at Arkansas, um, you know, I've
been able to we we've bu we've excelled
at wide zone, um, also inside zone. Um,
so I have a familiarity familiarity with
it. Um, so I I believe that I could come
in and, you know, really that that that
would be my advantage would uh, you
know, having a familiar with, you know,
run a wide zone at Arkansas.
What was it about Arkansas that enabled
you to kind of, you know, break out and
really find yourself uh last year as a
player uh and excel in the way that you
did?
>> I believe it it was a maturity thing. Um
understanding the game more um the ins
and out in ins and outs of it. Um and
really just being detailed about what I
need to do. And what I mean by that, you
know, obviously, you know, inside zone
is inside zone, but really taking it a
step further on who I need to read, um
what are my steps look looking like, how
I need to, uh, you know, do my steps
before I I get the ball, who I'm
reading. So things of that nature. I
feel like once I dove, um, deep into
that, like the detailed piece, that's
what made me really excel.
>> Hi, I have Heidi Fang, Las Vegas Review
Journal. Just wondering when you look at
Kubak um and what he's done with running
backs particularly like Kenneth Walker
and uh Christian McAffrey and Zack
Charbanet last year with Walker as a
pairing just you know wondering what you
think about the styles the running backs
and what he does with um the position.
Um, I think it just speaks a lot about,
you know, what he can do, you know, and
my my goal, like I said before, like my
goal, I've been telling everybody like
um I'm I'm looking to be a legend and
I'm going to be a legend, you know. So,
um I definitely believe that he can
whatever he pulled out of them, he can
uh you know, do the same, you know, with
me. Also,
>> Mike Levi Edwards with Raiders.com. When
you think about the journey, obviously
you had to go to, uh, two other group of
six schools in Buffalo and North New
Mexico State before you got to Arkansas.
Throughout that journey, uh, getting to
the SEC, you know, what were some some
things that were instilled in you that
kind of helped you keep going? And, you
know, do you feel like even now going
into the league, you still have that
chip on your shoulder?
>> Yeah, I mean, I'm I'm I'm from New York,
so like, you know, coming up, I' i've
always had that chip on my shoulder. um
always just having that competitive
spirit um and just you know that
willingness to just want to do better
and you know that's something that just
it it won't it won't fade away. Um, you
know, also I'm I'm sure you you guys
probably seen, but you know, my brother,
you know, he's an ex-Marine, and you
know, growing up, all I would see was,
you know, him be disciplined. You know,
not motivated, but disciplined, cuz
motivated, our emotions. They come and
go. But discipline is me seeing him get
up at 6:00 a.m. in the morning every
single day and, you know, go work out
before going to high school, going to
class, you know. So, me seeing that,
that kind of has just been instilled in
me. And that's now now that's just who I
am now. So, that's something that just
won't fade away.
Hey. Uh, two questions. First one is
just real quick. Uh, I know you're
working on your masters at Arkansas. Did
are you going to get that?
>> Yeah. So, the plan is to, uh, get it
next spring, 2027. I should be done with
next spring.
>> And the other one is, um, you know, you
kind of referenced it of, you know,
seeing your brother work the way that he
did. But, uh, one of the things that's
been been said about you is, you know, a
lot of running backs might be flashy,
uh, a little bit, you know, over the top
like that. What is said about you is
that you're just quiet, put your head
down, just go to work, and that that's
how you like to go about your business.
I guess where did that come from and why
is that important to you?
>> Um really just being just being
misunderstood I feel like um you know
always just being overlooked you know
always just being you know the the the
last person to be picked you know it's
something that stems from when I was
younger you know and I kind of just like
I that's why like I kind of just
developed that mindset where where it's
like okay since I'm being overlooked and
nobody's looking at me I'm going make
you look at me by my work ethic.
>> Last one. Hondo, go ahead.
>> Mike, in doing my evaluation of you
before the draft, I heard a story that
after a big game at Arkansas, somebody
was talking about your stats and you
talked about it didn't matter because
you guys had lost the game that and they
said that you're extremely selfless.
It's about team. Does that come from
your brothers or spree decor background
with the Marines? Where does that come
from with you that you obviously looking
to an NFL career were even dismissive of
your success when the team didn't
succeed?
>> Yeah. Well, a lot of a lot of my my core
values stem from, you know, my my
brother, you know, him being a Marine
and, you know, also my parents, you
know, them being just hard workers. You
know, my dad is investigator and my
mother, you know, she has her PhD in
psychology and had um it's a total of
seven of us. Um I have six six other
siblings, you know, so just seeing them,
you know, work hard, but really outside
of that, you know, on a personal level,
um my my
I feel as though I would say I know as
though um just I just have a competitive
spirit. So like regardless of me having
a good game, like it doesn't matter if
we didn't if we didn't win. I'mma look
at like, you know, the Texas A&M game. I
had like 140 and something yards and you
know we didn't win. I was pissed like
you know like I I was I was I was hurt
that like that game hurt you know. Yeah
I had a big game but we didn't win. That
was a ranked opponent that I knew we we
should have beat you know we didn't win
and that's just that that passion and
that you know hunger to just want to
succeed and just want to win not only
for myself but as a team.
>> Awesome. Thanks so much. I really
appreciate you.
>> All right. Thank you.